yunjaelove.com 2013-09-06

# None

In this document, Domain Names International is referred to as “DNI”.

DNI respects your privacy. We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for marketing purposes without your explicit consent. By law, domain name registration information must be made available through Whois, a publicly accessible database that lists the domain name registration information of each registrant. Since domain name registration information is available to the public through Whois, anyone can access it on other web resources that offer Whois. Therefore, the domain name registration information you provide us is, and must be, made available to the public. At times our customers may be included within searches of the Whois database; however, any "spam" received through the use of Whois does not originate from DNI.

The privacy policy of this statement applies to our services offered under the domain name DNI and to our subsidiaries or joint venture websites. We promise that we will not use your personal information in any way that is incompatible with this privacy policy. By visiting this website you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this privacy policy. This privacy policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the DNI Universal Terms of Service (“UTOS”) Agreement. Please do not use or access the DNI website if you do not agree to the UTOS or to this privacy policy.

DNI does not create individual profiles for visitors. We only collects aggregate data.  Because your trust and confidence is important to us, DNI conducts its business under the following privacy principles: 

**Principle 1 - No Collection of Personal Information**

DNI does not collect any personal information such as names, ages, phone numbers, addresses, or e-mail addresses from visitors to our website.

**Principle 2 - No Combination of Browsing and Web Traffic Information with Personal Information**

Since DNI does not collect any personal information from website visitors, we do not combine traffic analysis information with personal information such as name, age, phone number or mailing address.

**Principle 3 - No Aggregation of Individual Visitor Traffic Patterns across Multiple Sites**

DNI does not collect individual profile information for visitors across multiple sites and does not aggregate information from any other sources about browsing patterns of individual visitors across multiple sites.

**Principle 4 - Collection of Non-Personally Identifiable Information**

DNI collects anonymous visitor information including IP addresses, browser types (such as Internet Explorer or Netscape), referring pages, pages visited, and time spent on the web site. DNI collects this non-personally identifiable information for the following purposes: (1) to provide anonymous statistical analysis of web page traffic patterns for our website; (2) to administer our website and servers, (3) to allow for auditing of our services by third parties, and (4) to improve our services.

**Principle 5 - Anonymous Use of Cookies**

It is DNI's policy to use cookies only for more accurate anonymous traffic analysis such as tracking the time/date of the visit, the page viewed, the referrer, and transaction information for eCommerce pages. The cookie information does not include personal data such as name, age, phone number, e-mail address or mailing address. In addition, DNI does not link cookies to personal data such as name, age, phone number, e-mail address or mailing address. Because we do not build a database of individual visitors, the data that we do collect is never stored in any individual user profile; the data collected serves only to update aggregate counts allowing us to monitor traffic on our site.

**Principle 6 - No Individual Profiling**

DNI does not create individual profiles of visitors. Unlike other tracking services we do not have a database of individual profiles of each visitor. DNI collects data in aggregate form, and data is not recorded or stored about individual visitors.

**Notices:**

**Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement**

We cooperate with government and law enforcement officials when legally required to do so. This includes disclosing any information necessary or appropriate to enforce our Universal Terms of Service, or in response to subpoenas, claims and other legal process, to protect our own property and rights or the property and rights of any third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we consider to be illegal or unethical. We also share your information to the extent necessary to comply with ICANN's rules, regulations and policies.

**Transfer of Data Abroad**

If you are visiting any DNI website from a country other than the country in which our servers are located, any communication with us may result in the transfer of information across international borders.  By visiting any DNI website and communicating electronically with us, you consent to such transfers.

DNI may amend this privacy policy at any time by posting the amendment terms to our website.

For your safety and protection, your credit card information is not stored on our servers. Our payment gateway provider, Durango Merchant Services, keeps this information encrypted and secure on your behalf.

Inquiries to DNI shall be made either by email, sent by first class mail to the physical address provided on the DNI Web site, or sent by first class mail to DNI's address at:

Domain Names International, Inc.

Legal Counsel

11605 Meridian Market View

Unit 124-134

Falcon, CO 80831

Revised: 4/12/2011

Copyright © 2011 Domain Names International.  All Rights Reserved.
